<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE document [
  <!ENTITY project SYSTEM "project.xml">
]>
<document url="index.html">

  &project;

  <properties>
    <title>Documentation Index</title>
  </properties>

<body>

<section name="Introduction">

<p>This is the top-level entry point of the documentation bundle for the
	<strong>Cosmo</strong> sharing server.
</p> 

</section>

<section name="What is Cosmo?">

<p>Cosmo is a calendar server. With your favorite calendar program
(Chandler, Apple iCal, Mozilla Sunbird, or any other WebDAV or CalDAV
enabled client), you can share your calendar with other people by
publishing it to Cosmo. Once your calendar is stored on the server,
you can give permission for others to subscribe to it, and even modify
it if their calendar client allows.
</p>

<p>Cosmo is a file server. You can store arbitrary files in your home
directory in Cosmo with any WebDAV client (including the Windows XP,
Linux and Apple OS X file managers), and you can share them with
others in the same way as your calendar.
</p>

<p>Cosmo is not a web-based personal information manager. It is a server
that such an application could use to store and access many users'
information over the Internet. OSAF's Scooby project aims to provide
an innovative web interface for calendaring and will be tightly
integrated with Cosmo.
</p>

<p>Cosmo is not a content management system. There is no support for
common CMS features such as versioning, content editing or
workflow. Cosmo very simply allows calendar and file management
applications to publish and subscribe to a content repository.
</p>

</section>

<section name="Reference">
<ul>
<li><a href="README.txt"><strong>README</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="http://cosmo.osafoundation.org/release_notes.php"><strong>Release notes</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="apidocs/index.html"><strong>API Documentation</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="http://wiki.osafoundation.org/bin/view/Documentation/ServerBundleInstallation"><strong>Installation Help</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="http://cosmo.osafoundation.org/clientsetup.php"><strong>Client Setup</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="http://wiki.osafoundation.org/bin/view/Projects/CosmoFAQ"><strong>FAQ</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="http://lists.osafoundation.org/mailman/listinfo/cosmo-dev"><strong>Mailing List</strong></a></li>
</ul>
</section>

<section name="Licensing">
<p>
Cosmo is available under the terms of the <a href="http://apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0">Apache Software License, Version 2.0</a>.
</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="LICENSE.txt"><strong>LICENSE</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="NOTICE.txt"><strong>NOTICE</strong></a></li>
<li><a href="license"><strong>other licenses</strong></a></li>
</ul>
</section>

</body>
</document>
